what we need to create together is a
video chat scheduling app an app that
connects people on topics and a schedule
that worked for them
and uses existing video tech to have
those conversations on so an individual
can log on and say when they're
available what they want to talk about
it matches them with people or a group
of people can find a common time that
works for them why we need this is to
connect humanity over video chat it
helps us to do any of the future steps
we need to be able to come together as a
planet and solve any of our problems but
right now we are needing to have social
isolation due to the pandemic and people
are going to be feeling lonely and
disconnected what a great time to
connect them on a scale they have never
been connected and be able to empower
them to talk about topics that are of
interest and importance to them when I
want to do this is now I think that this
opportunity with us self isolating is
the perfect time to come together and
talk over video where we're not going to
be transmitting the virus and it can
connect us at a whole new level
how I need to find one person with the
and there's a few people I need to find
but especially the one person who has
the skills and the desire to create this
create the beta version of this some
very easy place where we can log in save
and we're available and the few topics
of interest to us and then it matches us
together where is global and online and
anyone can talk if somebody if it's 2:00
a.m. your time but it's the time you
prefer to talk and it's 3:00 p.m.
somebody else's time as long as we have
the topic of interest in common and as
long as we have the language we're
speaking in common we can connect we
already live in that world we just need
the organization which is what the tool
gives us and who I need who I need
that person who could actually create
this in a very small period of time in a
weekend in a week can create the
scheduling app who else I need would be
great if we could pay that person if or
have marketing to get people to know
this exists now during the social
isolation so if you're able to do a
crowdfunding campaign over this or
you're able to make this concept of a
scheduling app into a cute little
animated video that can go viral any of
those people did this speak to you can
you see the power of happiness right now
and the opportunity of this happening
during the pandemic contact me how you
contact me is at collaborative democracy
at gmail.com or on Twitter at crowd
democracy tweet at me or not if you're
not following me find me on Facebook and
don't friend me because I'm not gonna
probably accept you if you have no
friends in common but DM me Jubilee
Briscoe finds me let's coordinate let's
create the scheduling app they can
connect kick you manatee during this
time where we might feel even more
isolated than we were previously thank
you